ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 17, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: INFO '85: A folder of facts and figures on South Africa, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
    By J. B. Shapiro. Item is in English.
- Box: 18, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Directory of TWARO Affiliated Organizations, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). Item is in English.
- Box: 18, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). Photocopy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.27/5/88 (1988:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.27/9/88 (1988:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.27/8/88 (1988:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.27/7/88 (1988:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.27/6/88 (1988:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.28/4/89 (1989:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.28/3/89 (1989:Apr./May). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.28/2/89 (1989:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.28/1/89 (1989:Jan./Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.29/5-6/90 (1990:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.29/3-4/90 (1990:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.29/1/90 (1990:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.29/2/90 (1990:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/7/91 (1991:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/4-5/91 (1991:Apr./June). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/3/91 (1991:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/2/91 (1991:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/1/91 (1991:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/10/91 (1991:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/11-12/91 (1991:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.30/8-9/91 (1991:Aug./Sep.). Item is in English.
- Box: 18, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/12/92 (1992:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/11/92 (1992:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/8-10/92 (1992:Aug./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/6-7/92 (1992:June/July). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/5/92 (1992:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/1/92 (1992:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.31/2-4/92 (1992:Feb./Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/10-12/93 (1993:Oct./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/8-9/93 (1993:Aug./Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/6-7/93 (1993:June/July). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/4-5/93 (1993:Apr./May). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/2-3/93 (1993:Feb./Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.32/1/93 (1993:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/2/94 (1994:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/3-6/94 (1994:Mar./June). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/7/94 (1994:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/8-10/94 (1994:Aug./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/11-12/94 (1994:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.33/1/94 (1994:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.35/4-5/95 (1995:Apr./May). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.35/1/95 (1995:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.35/2/95 (1995:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: TWARO News, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
    By TWARO (Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation of the ITGLWF). no.35/3/95 (1995:Mar.). Item is in English.
- Box: 18, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 20th Anniversary Souvenir Magazine, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Constitution, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Future Activities of TWARO, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Recommendations and Guidelines on Organising Strategies and Tactics, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Report of The 2nd TWARO Fact-Finding Mission To The People's Republic of China, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Report of The 2nd TWARO Fact-Finding Mission to the People's Republic of China, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Structure and Activities, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: TWARO Action Programme, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: TWARO Policy Statement and Conclusions, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Box: 19, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Consensus for Change, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Budapest Statement on Human Development in a Changing World, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By North South Roundtable. 6-9 September 1987. North South Roundtable, UNDP Development Study Programme. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Catalysts for Cooperation, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Decade Watch, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). v.7:no.2 (1988:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Heading for Change, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Human Development At Work, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Salzburg Statement on Adjustment and Growth with Human Development, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By North South Roundtable. 7-9 September 1986. North South Roundtable, UNDP Development Study Programme. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Amman Statement on Human Development Goals and Strategies for the year 2000, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
    By North South Roundtable. 3-5 Spetember 1988. North South Roundtable, UNDP Development Study Programme. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Challenge of the Environment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). October 1995 UN South Anniversary Issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). May 1995, Special Issue: New Directions. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Cooperation South, Special Section: The Environment in Focus, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). April 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). December 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). November 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). May 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Cooperation South, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). September 1994, Special Issue. Item is in English.
- Box: 19, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Source, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Source, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). July 1992. Item is in English.
- Box: 19, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). November 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). July 1992, Special Report: The Uprooted Photo Essay. Item is in English.
- Box: 19, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). December 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). September 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). June 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). March 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). June 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). September 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). Dcember 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By UNDP (United Nations Development Programme). March 1994. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Working Women Count! A Report to the Nation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    By Women's Bureau U.S. Department of Labor. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Empowerment of Women in the International Trade Union Movement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    By FNV Fonds de Solidarite Internationale. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Plus de Pouvoir aux Femmes dans le Mouvement Syndical International, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    By FNV Fonds de Solidarite Internationale. Item is in French.
- Box: 20, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Working Woman's Guide to Her Job Rights, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    By Women's Bureau U.S. Department of Labor. Leaflet no.55. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Home-Based Employment, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    By Cynthia B. Costello. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Caderno da Cut: Mulher Trabalhadora, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    By Central Unica dos Trabalhadores. Item is in Portuguese.
- Box: 20, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Asia's Working Women Demand a Share in the Economic Miracle, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Beyond Labour Issues: Workers In Asia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    By Committee For Asian Women. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Women in the Labour Force, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
    By Women's Bureau Labour Canada. Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Las Mujeres Que Trabajan, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Mujer El Trabajo Te Identifica El Sindicalismo Te Organiza, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Mujeres Trabajo y Sindicalismo: America Latina y el Caribe, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). no.3 (1989:Aug.). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Mujeres Trabajo y Sindicalismo: America Latina y el Caribe, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). no.1 (1989:May). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Mujeres Trabajo y Sindicalismo: America Latina y el Caribe, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). no.2 (1989:May). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Mujeres Trabajo y Sindicalismo: America Latina y el Caribe, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). no.4 (1989:Aug.). Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 20, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.8:no.1 (1989:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.8:no.3 (1989:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.9:no.2 (1990:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.9:no.3 (1990:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.10:no.2 (1991:Jume). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.10:no.1 (1991:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.11:no.3 (1992:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.11:no.4 (1992:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.10:no.4/v.11:no.1 (1992:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.12:no.4 (1993:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.12:no.3 (1993:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.12:no.2 (1993:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.13:no.3 (1994:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.14:no.2 (1995:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    By Asian Women Workers Newsletter. v.14:no.1 (1995:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Box: 20, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.2 (1990:May). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.2 (1990:May). Copy 2. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.3 (1990:June). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.3 (1990:June). Copy 2. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.4 (1990:Sep.). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.5 (1990:Nov.). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 7: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.1:no.1 (1990:Feb.). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 8: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.2:no.15 (1992:July/Aug.). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 9: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.3:no.18/19 (1993:Apr./July). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 10: Companeras, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    By CIOSL (Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres); ORIT (Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores). v.3:no.17 (1993:Jan./Mar.). Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 20, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. September 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. June 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.9 (1990:Dec.). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 4: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.11 (1991:Fall). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 5: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.14 (1992:Winter). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 6: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.13 (1992: Summer). Photocopy. Copy 3. Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 7: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.13 (1992: Summer). Photocopy. Copy 2. Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 8: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.13 (1992: Summer). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 9: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.15 (1993:Spring/Summer). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 10: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.16 (1994:May). Item is in English; Spanish.
  - Item 11: Correspondencia, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Interchange/Woman to Woman. no.17 (1995:May). Item is in English; Spanish.
- Box: 20, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Union Women on the Move, Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)